solestruck.com 2015-12-17

# Solestruck Customer Service - we aim to please.

### THE SOLESTRUCK PRIVACY NOTICE

Because Solestruck understands that the privacy of your personal information is important to you, we have established privacy policies and practices. This notice explains how your data will be used and shared by Solestruck. By visiting Solestruck.com, you accept the policies and practices described in this Privacy Notice.

### Information We Collect

Personal information is collected when you sign in to Solestruck.com, upon registration with Solestruck, when placing an order, or when contacting us via phone or email. Additional personal identification information such as user name, password, billing information, and contact information may also be collected in order to offer you Solestruck products and services. This information will be used to fulfill your orders, process your transactions, facilitate your use of our website, market our products and services, respond to your requests, assist you with future shopping, and improve Solestruck.com. Choosing not to provide us with information will limit our ability to respond to your shopping needs. In addition, information such as your IP address and the site that referred you to ours will be gathered automatically. All data acquired via the website is stored indefinitely. Because of the nature of the Internet, data may pass through any country and any jurisdiction, including jurisdictions where privacy laws may be different and less protective than those of your home jurisdiction.

Unless you opt out of receiving promotional materials, we may send you information by email or postal mail to the address you provided. From time to time we may notify you of special promotions, new products or services, or other information that may interest you. You may also receive notifications of special promotions, new products, or additional services from our third-party associates. If you would like to opt out of receiving correspondence, please locate the "unsubscribe" link in the small grey text at the footer of our marketing emails or contact [ customerservice@solestruck.com ](mailto:customerservice@solestruck.com) for assistance.

We do not rent or sell your personal information to parties not associated with fulfilling your order, unless sharing this information is necessary to provide you with Solestruck products or is required by law. Solestruck also maintains contracts with third parties for billing, shipping, order processing, and other functions. Solestruck reserves the right to share your information with these third parties, in order to fulfill your order, provide related services, or when it is reasonably necessary to comply with legal process, respond to claims, or protect the rights, property or safety of our company, employees, customers, or the public.

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Any personal information or User Submissions that you voluntarily disclose on the Site becomes publicly available and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice. Solestruck cannot guarantee the security, privacy or confidentiality of your personal information or User Submissions. You post User Submissions at your own risk. Therefore, please be mindful of what you post, because it may become publicly available on the Site or otherwise. Even after removal, copies of your User Submissions may still be viewable in areas displayed outside the Site, in cached and archived pages, or if other Users have stored your User Submissions.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is automatically saved on your computer's hard drive when you visit a website. These cookies may contain information used to record the websites you visit, but do not contain any personally identifiable information such as your name, address, or credit card information. Solestruck uses cookies to give you a personalized shopping experience.

If you have signed up with Solestruck, cookies allow our website to recognize you when you return and give you access to your personal account options. Cookies also let our website remember the contents of your Shoe Box, allowing you to place orders more easily. We may also use cookies to keep track of the ways in which customers find us and navigate through our website. This information will be used internally to help us determine where improvements can be made to our online store.

If you do not wish cookies to be saved to your system, you may change your browser's settings so that your computer does not accept them. If cookies are disabled, however, you will not be able to purchase from our website and we will not be able to recognize you as a registered user.

### Links to Other Websites

There may be links to other websites from Solestruck.com. Solestruck does not control any third- party websites and we are not responsible for these sites' use of personal information. We encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of any linked site when you visit it.

### Children's Privacy

In order to protect the privacy of children on the Internet, we will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without the prior written consent of a parent or guardian. If we learn that a customer or registered user is actually under the age of 13, we will make every effort to delete all personal information for this person from our database, as our site is intended for adults over the age of 18.

### Ordering Over the Phone

If you prefer to order directly from Solestruck without using our website, you may call us toll-free at 1.800.494.1260. Our representatives are ready to take your order over the phone Monday through Friday 7am - 5pm PST.

### Solestruck Mailings

In order to keep our customers updated on our special offers, gifts, new items, and changes to our store, Solestruck may periodically send mail to registered users.

If you prefer not to receive Solestruck mailings and other communications, you may call our Customer Service department toll-free at 1.800.494.1260 and ask to be removed from our mailing list. Due to the nature of our mailing system, it may take six to eight weeks after removal from our mailing list to completely stop receiving mail.

### Privacy Notice Changes

This notice replaces all previous disclosures we may have provided you about our information practices. We reserve the right to revise and modify this policy at any time without notice and to apply these changes in policy to information previously collected, where legally permissible. We will notify you of changes by posting the policy changes on our website. This privacy notice was last updated on May 11, 2004.

The examples contained in our privacy notice are illustrations only, and are not intended to be exhaustive.

### Contact Us:

  * #### Solestruck Retail Store

417 SW 13th Ave.   
Portland, OR 97205  
p: 503.224.3591  
e: retail@solestruck.com 

  * #### Returns Address

Solestruck   
Returns Dept.   
7319 SW Kable Ln  
Suite 700  
Portland OR 97224 

  * Monday - Saturday: 11-7   
Sunday: 12-6 

  * E-Mail Us  
p: 800.494.1260
